seotoolscentral.com 2016-02-03

# Privacy Policy

In order to user our services at SEOToolsCentral, we will need to collect some information from you in order to help you with the services that you are inquiring about. We know that it is our responsibility to protect your privacy, so all the information that you provide us on SEOToolsCentral will be used towards the website analysis too. By using SEOToolsCentral, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

### Information Collection

SEO ToolsCentral, collects and uses website information to operate its website analysis tool and deliver the services you have requested. This information can include: IP address, domain names, estimated visitors, in-site and off-site SEO analysis, usability, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used by SEOToolsCentral for the operation of its service and to provide general statistics regarding use of the SEOToolsCentral web tool.

### Use of Personal Information

SEOToolsCentral, does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. SEOToolsCentral may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. Such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to SEOToolsCentral, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

SEOToolsCentral web tools will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on SEOToolsCentral or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of SEOToolsCentral (including enforcing this agreement); and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of SEOToolsCentral, or the public.

### Security of your Personal Information

SEOToolsCentral uses a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. SEOToolsCentral secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol. No method of safeguarding information is 100% secure.

### Changes to this Statement

SEOToolsCentral will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. SEOToolsCentral encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how SEOToolsCentral is protecting your information. When such a change is made, we will update the "Last Updated" date below. 

_Last Updated: April 1, 2010._
